Jewelry can be another one of the most fun things you can do with crocheting.
Now a lot of times you may see people making yarn into chokers and things.
However, what you may not realize is that you can use wire to crochet.
I like to use 28 gage wire.
And you can.
It comes in a silver tone, a gold tone and you can even get it in a copper tone.
And it's very simple and easy to do because its simply chaining.
What you do is you string your beads on your chain in the order you want them to be.
Then you chain a couple of chains.
Go around your bead.
Make another chain and continue on.
In these particular cases we have three chains in between each bead.
And I've used magnetic clasps to close the necklaces.
As well as toggle clasps for the bracelets.
The ring is made with stretchy elastic thread.
And you can wear it on any finger and impress your friends with your huge rock.